One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Zoro vs. Pica
Dressrosa
SMILE Factory
Now, you guys!
Are you ready?!
Yeah!
Take this despicable factory that caused you Tontattans so much pain...
and tear it down!
Let's go!
Thank you, Fraland!
Tontattans, good luck...
You handle the mess up there...
Luffy.
Help the injured first! Call the rescue team!
Aye!
Royal Palace Grounds
Showtime!
Half Moon...
Glaive!
Fourth Step
Sunflower Field
Kyros
vs.
Diamante
Kyros!
Just now, you were lashing out at me in rage.
Have you forgotten your place?
Did you think that I'm merely a talented matador who can make things ripple?!
You couldn't remain the Colosseum's strongest warrior forever, you know!
My skill is indisputable.
The current hero of the Colosseum is me, Diamante-sama!
I don't care about that title!
Of course, the rippling does help.
Father!
Nice try! You almost had me!
Well, of course it would come to this.
You've been running around the country all day,
and fighting me on this rippling arena while trying to keep your daughter safe!
And on just one leg, at that!
An ordinary person would have long since stopped moving.
Don't worry about my leg.
If I wanted to use it as an excuse,
I wouldn't have come to this battlefield!
I'm proud of my missing leg!
I gave it up for the man who saved my life!
I see. Then, I'll gladly aim for your weak spot.
It'd be no fun to kill you the old-fashioned way,
now that you're so worn out.
How about a game?!
The last showtime!
Is that...
Confetti?
That's right!
It's something that looks like paper, thanks to my ripple power.
And now, I'll undo my power.
Ripple Release!
Spiked iron balls!
Gaze upon their beauty! They're like stardust!
Robin-san!
Doesn't look like we can avoid it.
Robiland, please protect Rebecca!
Commander-san, you're in danger too!
I'll be fine!
You're panicking, I see. Very perceptive of you.
Yes, this stardust can slaughter entire armies!
It'd take a miracle for you to survive.
Thank goodness we're at the Sunflower Field.
Mil Fleur!
Thousand Flower
I'm sorry I have to pluck such magnificent flowers.
Struggle all you want!
Adios!
Death Enjambre!
Death Swarm
Flower Umbrella!
That was close!
Oh? Quite impressive.
Pay attention!
Kyros!
If an army were to fall to this kind of attack,
they'd be truly pathetic!
That's so crazy!
He's swatting away every single spiked iron ball!
Can he make it through a rain shower without even getting wet?!
Dammit!
Father!
Look out above, Kyros!
You klutz! How could you trip now?
Damn you, Diamante! I'll get you!
No, Rebecca! They're still falling!
Father!
You'll pay for this!
You'll pay for everything, Diamante!
Well said, Rebecca! Go ahead, make me pay!
Fight me! I'll kill you with my own two hands!
Just like I did your mother!
Let go of me, Robin-san! I'll kill him!
How long will this last?! The Flower Umbrella can't take any more!
Diamante!
This is my fight, Rebecca!
Drop...
your sword!
For an entire decade...
Father! Get under the umbrella! You'll die!
...you have followed your mother's wish!
Mother said that it's bad to hurt people.
I'm teaching you this so that you don't get hurt.
She's never hurt anyone,
and she's won all her battles by ring out!
She's the undefeated woman!
You can't even cut your enemy and you call yourself a winner?!
Shed some blood, Rebecca!
You coward!
That match was a complete disgrace!
You're the shame of all gladiators!
Drop dead, Rebecca!
Your family's a bunch of monsters!
You foul-blooded wench!
You've been fighting in the Colosseum, but you still haven't hurt anybody!
Your hands are still beautiful!
Those are the hands...
in which your mother Scarlett's spirit lives!
Mother...
After all your efforts, there's no need to bathe them in the blood of a devil like him.
Rebecca!
I'll make sure you never have to swing your sword again!
Kyros!
Are you made of iron?!
No, this guy is beyond insane...
The pain...
The pain is proof that I am human!
You people would never understand...
The despair of being forgotten by the ones you love!
Scarlett!
Why? Why didn't you wait for me?!
Of course.
I must have disappeared from your mind, too.
Both our promise... and our time together...
I don't know who you are...
It's me! It's Kyros!
Please...
With these tin arms,
I can't even feel your fading warmth!
You people don't understand...
The agony of being unable to feel anything you touch!
Or the tragedies that have befallen Dressrosa...
Compared to them,
this is not even pain!
If you want to say I'm made of something,
then I'll become this country's fury incarnate...
and bring you down!
How is he this strong?!
Your glory days were twenty years ago!
Don't underestimate my true skill with the sword!
You're still not dead?! You damn monster!
Just as the iron rain lifted, too.
I'll end this by killing you myself.
Just like Scarlett, who you two loved so much!
Diamante, you fiend!
How dare you bring up my sister again!
Damn you, Diamante!
I'm sorry, King Riku!
We searched as hard as we could, but all for naught! A man named Diamante got there before us,
and we found Scarlett-sama lying in the streets,
shot to death!
You killed my sister?!
Oh yeah, she was your older sister!
She was buying food at a market in the town.
If the fool could've controlled her hunger,
she wouldn't have had to die!
Let go of me, Tank!
Please stop! Don't do anything rash!
I can't take it anymore!
We'll stay in the palace, too.
To protect you!
Diamante!
My strikes rend the earth itself!
Take this, and that!
There!
Let's hope you can dodge my attacks...
With your single, shot-up leg!
I have no intention of dodging!
If you won't dodge, you're just an idiot!
I will return peace!
Half Moon Glaive!
Trueno...
Thunder
Bastardo!
Bastard
I owe you one, Robiland.
Father!
Father, we must tend to your wounds!
I couldn't protect your mother, but I'll protect you with my life.
Until the day you can find true happiness, I'll always be by your side.
He took down Diamante!
He took down the Diamante?
Is it true, Viola-sama?!
That's right! Kyros won!
Rebecca is okay, too.
Nico Robin protected her.
I can't believe he took down one of the Donquixote Family's top commanders!
He took down the hero of the Colosseum...
That's absurd!
Kyros was the original undefeated hero of the Colosseum!
We thought no one could beat the Donquixote Family...
but they're falling, one by one!
Kyros.
Army Commander Kyros!
Senor Pink lost the battle at the factory...
and many others of the Donquixote Family have been defeated by the warriors siding with Straw Hat Luffy.
There are four major opponents of the Donquixote Family left!
Bellamy the Hyena...
And the two top commanders, Pica and Trebol!
And...
the current king, one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea, Doflamingo!
The Final Four!
Never expected them to make it that far!
The Straw Hat Pirates are incredible!
I can't believe we were trying to save ourselves by killing them!
Well, like they say, we all make mistakes!
As long as you see the error of your ways, I'll forgive you!
Old King Riku, where are you going?
I don't think anyone will try to kill me now.
I'll go down to the town.
Surely there's still something I can do.
I shall accompany you!
I refuse to depend on the Government or the Navy!
Everybody's lost hope.
They think there's no escape from this bird cage, this deadly game!
We should all go too!
Let's tell everybody in the town there's still hope!
It would seem the tides have begun to turn.
Where did the Navy Admiral go?
Did you not notice?
He descended to the ground quite some time ago.
Gather all the citizens in one place.
Somewhere we'll be able to defend them.
Yes, sir!
Is he...
Royal Plateau
That bastard...
Fourth Step
Sunflower Field
Father, what are these tremors?
Rebecca!
That's...
But I thought Zoro was keeping him in check? Pica!
Diamante...
What a sorry state for a Family top commander.
Father!
I should have guessed.
We're not here to fight one-on-one!
As long as the enemy still stands,
the fight won't end!
Don't push yourself, Father!
You can't even move.
Stand down, Rebecca!
I have to ask.
What is King Riku to you people?
Rebecca, you had to endure unending jeers because of him.
If it weren't for him...
What nonsense! You people framed him!
King Riku is my father-in-law,
who stood by me since my days of thuggery!
The Royal Riku Family is revered worldwide as a family that understands the true meaning of peace!
A clear sky, flowers in full bloom...
A great country filled with gentle hearts!
That's what Dressrosa truly is!
Kicking you beasts out and returning him to the throne once more is our nation's desire this very moment!
I understand.
Huh? He vanished?
Charlestone!
Th-The hell is that?! That scared me!
Now he's on the third level!
Second Step
That damn bastard!
He's supposed to fight me!
Does he even want to fight?!
Either way, I can't reach him
if he's moving around in the plateau.
Prepare to die once you're back in range!
Charlestone!
Pica-sama, please stop!
Pica-sama!
Help!
That bastard! He's attacking the injured!
You betrayed us, Baby 5!
Steel Mill!
Look out!
Sai!
Charlestone!
That asshole!
You stony bastard!
That's enough outta you!
Quit going after the injured!
Roronoa.
Bite Stone!
One-Sword Style... Demon Horse!
Say, Roronoa Zoro...
Do you know who's on the old Royal Grounds?
The king of this country!
The former king!
What are you getting at?!
On the old Royal Grounds,
the former senior officials of this country are there,
as well as those samurai and God Usopp.
I heard the whole nation seeks
King Riku's restoration.
So what?!
That pisses me off! Doffy is the one and only king!
What the...
Bastard!
It started to move again!
Wh-What's he going to do?!
This is Donquixote country!
He's walking!
Run!
The statue's started to move! Run! Run for it!
Whoa, whoa, don't tell me...
That bastard!
So he's planning to take out the king?!
Bastard!
So that's why he drove me out this far!
I can't catch up to him!
I totally got played!
Gotta do something, or else...
It'll take him just one punch
to shatter the Royal Grounds!
Usopp and the king'll be crushed to death!
There any way to stop it?
Pirate Hunter!
We won't let you get in Pica-sama's way!
You're a pest!
Zoro!
Not good!
If we let him go, he'll...
Grandfather!
Usopp!
That bastard!
PLAN 1
Plan 1.
LONG DISTANCE SLASH
Long-distance slash.
PLAN 1
No, at that range, it would be far too weak.
It won't take him down.
JUMP
ON TOP
OF HIM
PLAN 2
Plan 2.
Jump on top of him.
Yeah that won't work.
PLAN 3
SHOUT OUT REAL LOUD
TO WARN USOPP
AND THE
OTHERS
PLAN 3 SHOUT OUT REAL LOUD
TO WARN USOPP SHOUT OUT REAL LOUD
DANGER
OF THE
OTHERS AND THE
DANGER OF THE
Plan 3.
SHOUT OUT REAL LOUD
TO WARN USOPP
AND THE
OTHERS
PLAN 3
DANGER
OF THE
Shout out real loud to warn Usopp and the others of the danger.
Usopp!
He'd never hear me from this distance.
AND TELL HIM
"GET THE HELL
BY SNAIL PHONE
AND TELL HIM BY SNAIL PHONE
"GET THE HELL OUTTA THERE"
CALL HIM PLAN 4
OUTTA THERE"
CALL HIM
PLAN 4
Plan 4.
AND TELL HIM
BY SNAIL PHONE
"GET THE HELL
Call him by Snail Phone and tell him,
"Get the hell outta there."
CALL HIM
OUTTA THERE"
PLAN 4
Oh, I don't have one.
Don't come any closer!
And even if I could tell him,
there's no time for everyone to get away!
Go for it!
Pica-sama!
He's going after King Riku!
It's none of our business,
but I still don't like it!
Stop, you stone monster!
Sogeking-senpai is on that plateau!
Stone! Come back here!
I'll fight you!
No!
I understand now!
The Pirate Hunter was right in
telling me to save my King Punch!
I'll save you, King Riku, my old friend!
Wait a sec, King of wherever!
"Wherever"?!
That's "King Elizabello of Prodence" to you, Pirate Hunter!
I told you, it's no use just destroying him.
He'll keep coming back
unless you beat him in the flesh!
Well, what should we do then?
Help me!
Pirate Hunter!
Hey!
Give me two minutes.
Is King Riku there?
Plan 5!
PLAN 5
FLY
Fly into the sky and dice this punk to bits!
INTO
THE
SKY
AND
DICE
THIS
PUNK
TO
BITS
FLY INTO THE SKY
AND DICE HIM
TO BITS!!!
PLAN 5 5
FLY INTO THE SKY AND DICE HIM
PLAN 555
PLAN 5
PLAN 5 5
FLY INTO THE SKY
AND DICE HIM
TO BITS!!!
That'll work!
If nothing is done...
Grandfather and everyone will...
Sogeking-senpai! Run!
Pirate Hunter!
How long will you make me wait?!
Hey, Director!
Huh? If you mean "Commodore," that's me.
Whatever!
Didn't you throw someone like a cannonball earlier?
Prepare yourself, King Riku!
Shoot! Shoot!
Your target is me, isn't it?!
Please stop causing all this destruction!
Everyone, out of here, now!
Evacuate the plateau!
King Riku, you must leave too!
Hurry, Father!
Viola, Tank!
Take everyone and descend at once!
His target is me! Go!
That's why you need to run, King Riku!
Please make haste!
No! If everyone else can escape
while he's targeting me,
then so be it!
I see! Then I'll do as you ask!
What the hell?
Pirate Hunter, Orlumbus!
Just what are you doing?
You really sure about this?
This technique isn't meant for throwing someone safely!
Just do it already! We don't have time!
That bastard!
He's only going after people
who don't want to fight!
Ready?
Yeah!
King Riku! You are no king!
You're not even fit to be king!
Commodore...
Your Majesty, if you won't run, then neither shall we!
King Riku, did you clear up the decade-long misunderstanding and win back your popularity?
A pacifist like you...
couldn't even protect his country!
Or have you forgotten?
A country is all about armed might!
A man that can't destroy his country's enemies...
is not qualified to be king!
I'll pulverize you and your cheap ideals!
King Riku!
Th-The town is falling!
Killer...
Bowling!
You're right!
I couldn't protect my country, so I'm incompetent! I have no intention of sitting on the throne ever again!
King Riku!
However...
I tried my best to be a good man!
The nine mountains and eight seas...
make one world!
A thousand of them form a small chiliocosm!
Note: Chiliocosm - Buddhist term for a cluster of a thousand realms.
And when I gather and cube that chiliocosm, there's nothing I can't cut!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
"Be a good man"?
If you say I'm not allowed to live without committing murder,
then I choose death!
There's no future for a mass-murdering nation!
Your Majesty! You are our one true king!
This is why the good never make history!
Because they all die like you!
Great Trichiliocosm...
One Billion Worlds!
Good! He's escaped into the upper body!
Roronoa!
Zoro!
Dead stones...
Living stones...
No matter how many pieces I carve him into, his real body definitely has to be in one of them!
He can't be in two pieces at once!
Whaaat?!
There's no ground in the air for him to hide in!
Show yourself, Pica!
How long will you keep hiding?!
By cornering me,
you think you've already won?!
You think you can beat me if you can cut those stones, don't you?
I can't be cut when I'm clad in Haki!
Haki, huh?
If I knock you off, you lose!
Only if your Haki is stronger than mine!
I don't have time to stumble over you here!
Quit babbling!
The nine mountains and eight seas...
There's nothing I can't cut!
Die!
Roronoa Zoro!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Stop troubling the innocent!
Zoro-senpai!
Doro!
The Pirate Hunter... saved my friend, King Riku?
It's still collapsing on us!
We're gonna die!
Help us, Boro!
Your turn!
King...
Punch!
That brat... He used my King Punch...
to clear away some rocks! How rude!
I won't forget this!
That's that!